# Krishna P Dulal

908 Monticello Ave, Charlottesville, VA | 571-249-7479 | krishnadulal2055@gmail.com

#### Summary

Upcoming BS in Computer Science graduate offering a strong foundation in software engineering and programming principles across multiple platforms. Experienced in object-oriented programming; developing, testing, and debugging code; designing interfaces; and administering systems and networks. Quickly learn and master new technologies, successful working in both team and self-directed settings.

### **Education**

# University of Virginia, School of Engineering and Applied Science, Charlottesville, VA

B.S. Computer Science | Cumulative GPA: 3.30 | May 2024

• Successfully managing 30 hours of work per week while pursuing studies at a top-tier university

## Northern Virginia Community College, Annandale, VA

A.S., Computer Science | Cumulative GPA: 3.49 | Aug 2020-May 2022

**Relevant Course:** Advanced Software, Database System, Data Structures and Algorithms, Computer Systems and Organizations, Discrete Mathematics

### **Technical Academic and Independent Projects**

### Data Structures and Algorithms, Python Projects | Nov 2022-present

• Completed data structure assignments, including Binary and Depth Search.

### Advanced Software, Java Projects | Nov 2022-present

• Developed CLI and GUI projects, like Wordle, Bus Route, Apportionment, and Puzzle Solver.

#### Game Library, Innovative Database Systems project | Summer 2023

 Manage game libraries and Wishlist's using Flask Framework. SQL commands for game data control.

#### Advisor Scheduler | Spring 2023

 Designed a conflict-free scheduling system using Django Framework. Integrated Google login for streamlined student-advisor connectivity.

#### **Work Experience**

#### Sales Associate - Virginia ABC, Charlottesville, VA

July 2021 – present

• Demonstrated exceptional leadership and multitasking abilities, earning the role of Lead Sales Associate within two years. Successfully balance daily operations with academic commitments.

#### Various Cashier/Server Roles

May 2019 - August 2022

• Obtained diverse experience in cashiering and serving, consistently providing top-tier service even in high-pressure situations.

### **Technical & Professional Skills**

Technical: Java, Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, MATLAB, Django, Flask, etc. Professional: Effective Communication, Time Management, Attention to Detail, Problem-Solving